This is what I get in return for 30 years of service for my company?
這就是我為公司干了30年得到的?
And they send some yo-yo like you in here,
他們派個像你這樣的混混
to try to tell me that I'm out of a job?
來告訴我 我已經不適合工作了?
They should be telling you you're out of a job.
他們應該告訴你 你才不適合工作了才對
You have a lot of gall, coming in here and firing your No.1 producer.
你居然有臉 來炒掉最能幫你賺錢的人
And then you're going to go home tomorrow and make more money than you've ever made in your life
然後明天就能帶著大筆鈔票回家了
and I'm going to go home without a pay cheque. Fuck you.
而我卻要身無分文的回去 我靠
I just... I guess you leave me dumbfounded. I don't know where this is coming from.
你.... 讓我目瞪口呆 不知道從何說起了
How am I supposed to go back as a man and explain to my wife that I lost my job?
做為一個男人 我該怎麼向老婆解釋 我被炒了?
On a stress level, I've heard that losing your job is like a death in the family.
從心理壓力上來說 我聽說丟掉工作 就像死了家人一樣
But personally, I feel more like
不過我個人覺得
the people I worked with were my family and I died.
更像我的同事們是家人 而我死了
I can't afford to be unemployed.
我不能失去這份工作
I have a house payment, I have children.
我要還房貸 還要養孩子
I don't know how you can live with yourself,
我不知道你過得怎麼樣
but I'm sure that you'll find a way while the rest of us are suffering.
但是我肯定 在我們受折磨的時候 你能過得很好
Who the fuck are you, man?
你他媽的是誰?
Excellent question. Who the fuck am I?
好問題 我他媽的是誰?
Poor Steve has worked here for seven years.
可憐的Steve在這兒工作七年了
He's never had a meeting with me before or passed me in the hall,
我們從來沒一起開過會 或者在走廊裡遇見過
or told me a story in the break room.
或者在休息室裡聊過天
That's because I don't work here.
因為我其實不在這裡上班
I work for another company that lends me out to pussies like Steve's boss
我所在的公司專門幫助那些 像Steve的老闆一樣的膽小鬼們
who don't have the balls to sack their own employees,
炒掉自己的員工
in some cases for good reason. Because people do crazy shit when they get fired.
可以幫他們一勞永逸 人們被炒的時候 抓狂是理所當然的
Did I do something wrong?
我做錯什麼了嗎?
I mean, is there something I could do differently here?
我是說 我做得比其它人差麼?
This is not an assessment of your productivity. Try not to take this personally.
這不是針對你的 與你的工作能力無關
Don't take it personally.
不是針對個人的
Steven, I want you to review this packet.
Steven 我想請你看下這份材料
Take it seriously. I think you're gonna find a lot of good answers in here.
請仔細看看 這裡有你想知道的答案
I'm sure this is gonna be very helpful. A packet.
我知道這肯定很有用 有一包呢
Thank you... A packet.
謝謝... 你的一包材料
Well, anybody who ever built an empire or changed the world sat where you are right now.
那些曾建立帝國 改變世界的偉人們 也有過你這樣的遭遇
And it's because they sat there they were able to do it.
也正因為他們經歷過 他們才能做到
That's the truth.
真的
I'm gonna need your keycard.
請把你工牌給我
Great. OK.
好極了
Now, I want you to take the day, go get together your personal things, then tomorrow
現在 我希望你好好利用今天 收拾下你的東西
you get yourself some exercise. You go out for a jog,
明天鍛煉鍛煉 出去跑跑
you give yourself some routines and pretty soon you find your legs.
每天生活得規律點 很快你就能找回自信
- How do I get in touch with you?  - Don't worry, we'll be in touch soon.
- 我怎麼聯繫你?  - 別擔心 我們會聯繫你的
This is just the beginning.
這只是個開始
I'll never see Steve again.
我再也不會見到Steve了
To know me is to fly with me. This is where I live.
想瞭解我就要和我一起坐飛機 飛機就是我的家
When I run my card,
當我刷卡的時候
the system automatically prompts the desk clerk to greet me with this exact statement:
系統會自動提醒前台小姐向我問好:
Pleasure to see you again, Mr Bingham.
很高興再次見到你 Bingham先生
It's these kinds of systemised friendly touches that keep my world in orbit.
正是這些系統化的友好問候 使我的生活保持了規律
All the things you probably hate about travelling
你可能會因為這些而討厭旅行
the recycled air, the artificial lighting, the digital juice dispensers,
循環空氣 人工照明 全自動果汁機
the cheap sushi... are warm reminders that I'm home.
廉價壽司... 正是它們提醒了我 這才是家
Do you want the cancer?
你想要cancer(癌癥)麼?
- The what?  - Do you want the cancer?
- 什麼?  - 你想要cancer(癌癥)麼?
The cancer?
癌癥?
- The can... sir?  - Oh, no. I'm fine, thank you.
- 這瓶飲料... 先生?  - 哦 不用了 謝謝
How much does your life weigh?
你的生活有多重?
Imagine for a second that you're carrying a backpack.
想像下你正背著一個包
I want you to feel the straps on your shoulders. Feel 'em?
我要你們想像一下 背帶勒在肩膀上 感覺到了麼?
Now I want you to pack it with all the stuff that you have in your life.
現在我想讓你們 把生活中所有的東西都塞到包裡
Start with the little things,
從小件開始
the things on shelves and in drawers the knick-knacks, the collectibles.
比如書架裡抽屜裡的小玩意收藏品
Feel the weight as that adds up.
感覺背包不斷變重
Then you start adding larger stuff... clothes, table-top appliances, lamps, linens...
然後開始收拾大件的... 衣服 桌上電器 檯燈 毛巾...
your TV...
電視...
The backpack should be getting pretty heavy now. And you go bigger.
背包現在已經相當重了 接著收拾更大的
Your couch, bed, your kitchen table. Stuff it all in there.
沙發 床 餐桌 全都放進去
Your car, get it in there.
車也放進去
Your home, whether it's a studio apartment or a two-bedroomed house.
你的房子 不管是間單人公寓 還是套兩居室
I want you to stuff it all into that backpack.
我想讓你們全都塞進背包裡
Now try to walk.
現在試著走兩步
It's kind of hard, isn't it?
很困難 是吧?
This is what we do to ourselves on a daily basis.
這就是我們每天做的事情
We weigh ourselves down until we can't even move. And make no mistake...
我們不斷給自己增重 直到寸步難行 而且不能犯錯...
moving is living.
移動就是生命
Now, I'm gonna set that backpack on fire. What do you want to take out of it?
現在 我要把這背包燒了 你們想從裡面拿出來什麼?
Photos?
照片?
Photos are for people who can't remember. Drink some ginkgo and let the photos burn.
照片是給沒記性的人準備的 喝點銀杏飲料(防治高血壓 心臟病) 燒了照片吧
In fact, let everything burn and imagine waking up tomorrow with nothing.
事實上 燒掉所有東西 想像著明天醒來什麼都不必擔負
It's kind of exhilarating, isn't it?
很令人興奮 對嗎?
Welcome back, Mr Bingham.
歡迎回來 Bingham先生
- Ryan Bingham's office.  - You have me in a Dodge Stratus in Kansas City.
- Ryan Bingham工作室  - 你讓我在堪薩斯坐道奇Stratus(一種轎車)啊
- They were out of all full-size sedans.  - Did you try...
- 那裡沒有全尺寸轎車了  - 你試過...
Yes, I reminded them of your remarkable No.1 Gold Club status in years in the program.
是的 我提醒過他們 你是一號黃金俱樂部的資深會員
They are literally moving mountains to see you in a Sebring.
他們正竭盡全力 要給你找輛鉑銳(一種轎車)呢
- Fair enough. Any other messages?  - Er... your sister Kara called.
- 可以了 還有其它消息麼?  - 呃... 你妹妹Kara找你
Needs to speak urgently about your sister's wedding.
迫切想要和你談談她的婚禮
I told her you were mid-air, and not even I knew your destination.
我告訴她你正在航班上 我也不清楚是飛去哪裡的
- Well done.  - You got an invitation to speak at GoalQuest in Vegas.
- 幹得不錯  - 你被邀請 去維加斯的GoalQuest上演說
GoalQuest 20?
GoalQuest 20?
Every once in a while, I do speaking engagements, motivational stuff. But GoalQuest?
我時不時的被邀請進行一些激勵演說 不過GoalQuest?
We're talking major Tony Robbins shit.
那可是最大腕的演講會啊
It's got a hologram on it. They're calling it Dos Equis.
請帖上有個全息照防偽標誌 叫做Dos Equis
- All right, I'll check in.  - I've got Craig Gregory for you.
- 好的 我會去的  - Craig Gregory找你
Wait... ah. Fuck.
等等... 啊 我靠
How is my little road warrior?
我的小遊俠怎麼樣了啊?
Hey, 20 minutes from boarding into a world of bliss.
嘿 20分鐘以後登機上天
Real good numbers out of Phoenix, Ry guy.
在菲尼克斯做的不錯啊 夥計
You know that Big Auto is about to cut another 10K by the end of the month?
你知道Big Auto月底又要裁1萬人了嗎?
- No kidding.  - Christmas came early.
- 不會是真的吧  - 聖誕節快到了
I wish you could be in five places, but I do need you here in Omaha this week. Alright?
我希望你能分身五處 不過這周我需要你待在奧馬哈 沒問題吧?
- I thought you needed me everywhere.  - We got something real big, a real game changer.
- 我看你是想我分身無數個吧  - 我們有個大計劃 準備大換樣了
What are we talking about here?
你在說什麼呢?
You'll see. Today I took my first crap in two weeks. Hallelujah.
等著瞧吧 兩個星期了 我終於拉了一泡屎 哈利路亞
- That's me hanging up on you.  - Great, love that sound.
- 我要掛電話了  - 最愛聽掛電話的聲音了
Are you satisfied with Maestro?
對Maestro(美國汽車租賃公司)滿意麼?
Yeah, I am.
是的
A little stingy with their miles. I like Hertz.
它們的里程算得很嚴啊 我喜歡Hertz(美國汽車租賃巨頭)
No, Hertz keeps its vehicles too long. If a car has over 20,000 miles, I won't drive it.
不 Hertz的車太舊了 我從不開超過20000英里的車
Maestro doesn't instant checkout. I like the park-and-go.
Maestro不能即時結賬  我喜歡即停即走
- Hertz doesn't guarantee navigation.  - You don't seem like a girl who needs directions.
- Hertz不提供導航  - 你可不像需要導航的女士
I hate asking for directions. That's why I get a nav.
我討厭問路 所以我選擇導航服務
That new outfit, Colonial, isn't bad.
新公司 Colonial 還不錯
- Is that a joke?  - Yes.
- 你開玩笑的吧?  - 是的
- Their kiosk placement blows.  - They never have available upgrades.
- 他們的車亭很爛  - 也從不提供升級服務
Basically, it's a fleet of shit boxes. I don't know how they're still in business.
他們的車就像一隊破盒子 我真不明白為什麼它們還能營運
- I'm Ryan.  - I'm Alex.
- 我是Ryan  - 我叫Alex
Aww... Maplewood card. How dare you bring that into this palace?
呃... Maplewood酒店的卡 你怎麼能把這種卡 帶到這來?
Hilton offers equal value and better food but the Maplewood gives out warm cookies at check-in.
希爾頓的價格一樣 但食物更好 不過Maplewood在入住的時候 會送貼心的甜點
I'm a sucker for simulated hospitality.
我被假裝的好客迷住了
There's an industry term for that. It's a mixture of faux and homey... faumey.
其實這有個專業術語 是faux和homey結合起來的 叫faumey
Oh, my God. I wasn't sure this actually existed.
哦 天吶 我都不知道這卡確實有人有
- This is the American Airlines...  - It's a Concierge Key, yeah.
- 這是美國航空公司的...  - 對 這是貴賓卡
- What is that, carbon fibre?  - Graphite.
- 這是拿碳纖維做的?  - 石墨的
- Oh, I love the weight.  - I was pretty excited the day that bad boy came in.
- 哦 我喜歡這質感  - 拿到卡的時候我非常激動
I'll say. I put up pretty pedestrian numbers. 60 thousand a year, domestic.
確實 我的里程數也積攢了不少了 每年6萬 國內的
- That's not bad.  - Don't patronise me.
- 一般般吧  - 別忽悠我了
- What's your total?  - It's a personal question.
- 你積了多少了?  - 這是隱私
- Please.  - And we hardly know each other.
- 得了吧  - 而且我們還不熟
Show some hubris. Come on, impress me.
說出來聽聽 快 嚇嚇我
- I bet it's huge.  - You have no idea.
- 我猜肯定是個天文數字  - 你想像不到的
How big?
多大?
- What is it, this big? This big?  - I don't want to brag.
- 到底多大 這麼大? 還是這麼大?  - 我不想炫耀
Oh, come on! Come on.
噢 快啊! 說出來聽聽
Let's just say I have a number in mind. I haven't hit it yet.
我心裡有個目標 現在還沒達到
- This is pretty fucking sexy.  - Hope it doesn't cheapen our relationship.
- 這卡真性感  - 希望它不會讓我們的關係變低俗了
We're two people who get turned on by Elite Status. I think cheap is our starting point.
我們倆也算是成功人士了 我想低俗是我們的共同起點
There's nothing cheap about loyalty.
忠誠可沒有低俗的
So, we came up with this master plan, which was for me...
我們想出了這個計劃 給我...
to put gauze, to put bandages on both my hands.
兩手纏滿繃帶和紗布
Then we got on the plane, transatlantic, flying to erm... Zurich.
然後我們登機 橫渡大西洋 飛到了 呃... 蘇黎世
I waited till it was dark, and I walked up to the bathroom with her.
我一直等到天黑 然後我和她去到洗手間
Everybody was watching the movie and I was like...
大家都在看電影 而我就像殭屍一樣...
Opened up, went inside. She opened the door for me, and came in like she was gonna help me.
打開門進去 她幫我開的門 然後做出要幫我的樣子走進來
We gave it our best shot. It wasn't great. But it was fun. It was tricky.
我們覺得那樣酷極了 不是很棒 不過很有趣 很狡猾
- Give me some details.  - It's not so easy. Have you tried it?
- 再說說細節  - 不好形容的 你以前試過嘛?
- It's not so easy.  - Yes, I have.
- 不好說的  - 當然 我試過
- Really?  - Really.
- 真的?  - 當然
- You've done that?  - I have done that.
- 你成功了?  - 是的
- On a transatlantic flight?  - On a domestic flight... regional, actually.
- 在跨洋航班上?  - 國內航班... 其實是地方航班
- At night-time?  - Daytime.
- 晚上?  - 白天
- What?  - How do you do that?
- 怎麼了?  - 你們怎麼做的?
Oh, I'm really flexible.
我很靈巧的
Look. Ohh.
瞧著 哦
Ah, I should throw these out.
啊 我應該扔了它們
We can always use that room with the ice machine.
我們可以用那間有製冰機的
Look.
你瞧
Good call on that towel rack.
毛巾架上叫得真激情啊
I like how you burritoed me in the sofa cushions.
我喜歡你在沙發上跟我翻雲覆雨
I was improvising.
那是即興的
Shame we didn't make it to the closet.
真遺憾我們沒在壁櫥裡做
- We got to do this again.  - Oh, yeah.
- 那我們得再來一次  - 哦 對
I'm in Newark on the 12th, Modesto on the 13th...
我第12周在紐瓦克 13周在莫德斯托...
Oklahoma City on the 15th...
第15周在俄克拉荷馬...
Any Southwest? I'll be swinging by Albuquerque week of the 16th.
哪天在西南區? 我第16周會到阿爾伯克基
No, I'm in Florida on the 20th.  - Fort Lauderdale?
沒有 第20周我會在佛羅里達  - 羅德岱堡 ?
- Miami. 40 minutes.  - That's nothing.
- 邁阿密 40分鐘車程呢  - 沒什麼區別
I should probably go back to my room so I can wake up in my bed.
我想我該回我房間了 這樣就能在自己的床上醒來
I think that would be the ladylike thing to do.
這才像淑女應該做的事情
- Nice meeting you.  - A pleasure.
- 很高興遇見你  - 我也是
Hello?
你好?
Hey, Ryan, how you holding up?
嘿 Ryan 最近怎麼樣?
Every family has one person who keeps the genealogy in check.
每個家庭都有一個成員經常保持聯繫
That's my sister Kara... the glue.
我妹妹Kara就是... 像萬能膠一樣
Fine. You and the kids?
我很好 你和孩子怎麼樣?
Missy's outstanding, Matthew made varsity. How's the road?
小姑娘棒極了 Matthew進了校運動隊 旅途順利嗎?
Couldn't be better.
好極了
Good. So, Ryan?
很好 那麼 Ryan?
Yeah?
嗯?
I didn't even want to ask you this, because I know how you are about doing things for others.
其實我不想問你 我知道你對於幫別人忙的態度
But we're coming up on three weeks to go to Julie's wedding and something we could really use your help on it.
可是3個星期後就是Juli的婚禮了 我們需要你的幫忙
Yeah?
什麼?
We've been sending people these kits,
我們寄給人們一些小東西
so they can print out photos of Julie and Jim on cardboard,
這樣就可以把Julie和Jim的相片打在紙板上
and then take photos of them in interesting places, kinda like that gnome in the French movie.
然後就可以在有趣的地方照相 比如法國電影裡的地精
Why?
為什麼?
Because it's Julie's wedding and she thinks it would be fun. Does it matter why?
因為這是Julie的婚禮 她覺得這很有趣 需要原因嗎?
How is Julie?
Julie怎麼樣了?
Would you call her. She thinks you've turned to butter.
你不能打個電話給她麼 她覺得你像溜走了似的
- You're awfully isolated the way you live.  - Isolated? I'm surrounded.
- 你簡直就是孤僻透頂  - 孤僻? 完全不
So your assistant said you were gonna be in Vegas.
你的助手說你要去維加斯
Did he?
他這麼說過?
Can you get a photo of the cut-out in front of the Luxor pyramid?
你能在盧克索酒店前照張相麼?
The place is a shithole. Nobody stays there.
那地方就像糞坑一樣 沒人會住那
Jesus, Ryan, I'm not asking you to check in. Can you just take a stupid photo?
天吶 Ryan 我不是讓你住在那裡 你不能只拍一張照片麼?
I'll try my best.
我會盡力的
Thank you for trying your best.
謝謝你的努力
Last year, I spent 322 days on the road,
去年 我有322天在旅途中
which means I had to spend 43 miserable days at home.
也就是說我要在家待痛苦的43天
Hey, neighbour.
嘿 鄰居
Hey, hi.
嘿 你好
- I signed for this while you were gone.  - Oh, thanks.
- 這個是你出差時候我簽收的  - 哦 謝謝
- I hope it wasn't too much of a bother.  - Nah.
- 希望沒有麻煩到你  - 沒有
It's my sister. I haven't met the guy yet. They're getting married.
這是我妹妹 我還沒見過她未婚夫 他們要結婚了
- Lots of luck.  - I know, right?
- 不錯啊  - 是嗎?
What are you doing tonight? You wanna come over later?
你今晚有空嗎? 一會過來聊聊?
Um... I've started seeing somebody.
呃... 我最近開始談戀愛了
Oh. OK. Great.
哦 好啊 太棒了
Hey, it's good to see you.
嘿 見到你很高興
- You too.  - It seems like it's been a while this time.
- 我也是  - 這次好久沒來見你了啊
Ok.
好的
I'm thrilled that everyone's back under one roof. Welcome home, boy's.
大家又聚到一起了 我很激動 兄弟們 歡迎回家
There's been a lot of whispering about why we're here, so let me jump right in.
關於為什麼我們會在這裡 有很多謠言 所以我開門見山吧
Retailers are down 20%.
零售業下降了20%
Auto industry is in the dump. Housing market doesn't have a heartbeat.
汽車業也不景氣 房地產已經完了
It is one of the worst times on record for America.
這是美國有史以來最糟糕的經濟危機之一
This is our moment.
這是我們的機遇
Now, last summer, we received a dynamite young woman here from Cornell.
去年夏天 我們這兒來了一位康奈爾大學畢業的女孩 活力四射
And she had some pretty big ideas that she challenged me with.
她向我提出了一些很有創意的想法
My first reaction was, "Who does this kid think she is?"
我的第一反應是 "她以為她是誰?"
But after I gave it a listen, she really knocked me out. So...
後來我仔細聽了聽 她確實震撼到我了 所以...
With a peek into our future, Natalie Keener.
有請我們未來的希望 Natalie Keener
If there's one word I want to leave you with today, it's this.
今天我想對大家說的 只有這一個詞
Glocal?
Glocal?
Glocal.
Glocal
Our global must become local.
我們的全球化必須本地化
This company keeps 23 people on the road at least 250 days a year.
我們公司有23個人 一年出差250天以上
It's expensive and it's inefficient.
這是昂貴且低效的
When I came to Craig three months ago with this,
當我三個月前 帶著此建議找Craig的時候
he told me, and quite astutely, it's only a problem if you have a solution.
他很狡猾的回答我 只有你能解決它的時候 這才是個問題
Well, today I stand before you with just that.
現在 我帶著解決方法站在你們面前
You all know Ned in reception. Today I'm gonna fire Ned.
你們都認識接待處的Ned 今天我要來炒掉他
Sorry, Ned. I'm sure HR will hire you back this afternoon.
抱歉 Ned 我肯定今天下午 人事部會重新僱請你
We'll see about that.
這可未必
Ned could be any employee in any one of our clients' locations worldwide.
Ned可以是我們任何地方的客戶 想要解雇的任何一人
Strategy packets will be shipped in advance.
策略規劃會提前送達
Ned will be given a seat and find one of our transition specialists waiting.
Ned一坐下就會看到 我們一個過渡專家正在等他
Mr Laskin,
Laskin先生
we're having this conversation as your position is no longer available.
今天我們進行對話 是因為你的職位已經不再需要了
I don't understand. I'm fired?
我不明白 我被炒了?
Hearing the words"You've been let go" is never easy.
聽到"你已經被趕走了"這句話確實不好受
Change is scary, but consider the following:
改變讓人恐懼 但是要考慮一下:
anybody who ever built an empire or changed the world sat where you are now.
那些曾建立帝國 改變世界的偉人們 也有過你這樣的遭遇
And it's because they sat there that they were able to do it.
也正因為他們經歷過 他們才能做到
That's my fucking line.
那他媽是我的台詞
But what happens now?
但現在是怎麼回事?
This is the first step of a process that ends with you in a new job that fulfils you.
你要做的第一步就是 找到適合你的新工作
Yeah, but how does it work?
是 但怎樣才能做到?
Way to take the packet in front of you.
打開你面前的文件包
Review it... all the answers you're looking for are inside.
仔細看看... 你要的答案都在裡面
Start to fill out the necessary information and before you know it, you're on the way to new opportunities.
填上必要的信息 你就踏上尋找新機遇的路了
Ned, go back to your desk and start putting together your things.
Ned 回到你的辦公桌 開始收拾你的東西
As a favour to me, I'd appreciate it if you didn't spread the news just yet.
就當是幫我 我希望你現在別把這事傳出去
Panic doesn't help anyone.
恐慌幫不了任何人
I understand.
我明白
Give it up for Ned.
為Ned鼓掌
You can start the morning in Boston, stop in Dallas over lunch,
你可以一早從波士頓開始 午後去達拉斯
and finish the day in San Francisco. All for the price of a T1 line.
在舊金山結束一天的工作 只需要支付T1網絡的費用
Our inflated travel budget is eviscerated by 85%.
我們的出差預算減少了85%
And more importantly, to you guys on the road,
更重要的是 對奔波在外的你們來說
no more Christmases in a hotel in Tulsa, no more hours lost to weather delays.
再也不用在塔爾薩的賓館裡過聖誕 再也不會因為天氣耽誤時間
You get to come home.
你們可以回家了
Tell me you're not taking this seriously.
告訴我你不是動真格的
That's why I brought the entire company in from the road,
我把全公司的人從路上拉回公司
because we're taking it seriously.
就是因為要動真格的
There is a methodology to what I do, there is a reason why it works.
我做的工作有一套方法論 有它行之有效的原因
Coke and IBM have been doing this for years, alright? You're familiar with them?
可口可樂和IBM這麼做很多年了 好嗎? 對它們不陌生吧?
Like anything else, it'll take a few months of transition and everybody will settle in.
新東西都這樣 需要幾個月的過渡期 大家都會適應的
- Who are you taking off the road?  - How are you not getting this?
- 你要把誰從路上拉回來?  - 你怎麼還不明白?
You are grouned. Everybody's grounded. It's done.
你不用到處跑了 所有人都不用到處跑了 就這麼定了
What we do here is brutal and it does leave people devastated.
我們這樣做太殘酷了 會讓離職的人們身心交瘁
But there is a dignity to the way I do it.
而我的方式卻能給他們尊重
By stabbing them in the chest instead of the back, right?
不從背部 改從他們胸部捅一刀 是嗎?
- You wanted to see me?  - Well, uhm...
- 你要見我?  - 呃...
- You know what? Yeah, come on in. Come on in.  - Great job.
- 你知道嗎? 對 進來 進來  - 幹得漂亮
- Thank you. How's everyone taking it?  - Great.
- 謝謝 大家怎麼看?  - 非常好
Listen, I admire your... your zeal. And I think you have some very good ideas.
聽著 我很欣賞你的... 熱情 我認為你有些很不錯的想法
But you know nothing about the realities of my industry.
但你對我們行業的現實一無所知
You can set up an iChat, but you don't know how people think.
你可以建立聊天界面 但你不知道人們是怎麼想的
- Actually I minored in psychology.  - Nice.
- 我輔修了心理學  - 很好
- OK, kiddo, fire me.  - Ryan...
- 好吧 孩子 解雇我  - Ryan...
If she's gonna do this regularly, don't you wanna know if she can fire somebody?
如果她要經常這麼做 你難道不想知道她到底能不能勝任?
- She's fired Ned.  - My dog can fire Ned. Fire me.
- 她已經解雇了Ned  - 我的狗都能解雇Ned 解雇我
- You don't need to do this.  - No, it's OK. I got this.
- 你不必這麼做  - 不 沒關係 我做
Mr Bingham,
Bingham先生
I regret to inform you that your position at this company is no longer available.
很遺憾通知你 你的職位已經不需要人手了
Hm. Who the hell are you?
哼 你他媽是誰?
My name is Miss Keener. I'm here today to discuss your future.
我是Keener 我今天來這兒是要討論你的將來
My future? The only one who can fire me is Craig Gregory.
我的將來? 唯一能解雇我的是Craig Gregory
- Mr Craig Gregory hired me to handle this for him.  - Handle what? Handle me?
- Craig Gregory雇我來處理這些事  - 處理什麼? 解雇我?
Mr. Gregory hired me, he's the only one who can fire me.
Gregory先生僱用了我 他是唯一能解雇我的人
- You know what? I'm gonna go talk to him.  - Mr Bingham...
- 知道嗎? 我要和他談  - Bingham先生...
No, no. You can't follow me. You're on a computer screen, remember?
不 不 你不能跟著我 你只是在電腦屏幕上 記得吧?
- Ryan...  - Let's try this again. Fire me again.
- Ryan...  - 咱們再試試 再來解雇我
- I just did.  - Actually, you didn't. Fire me.
- 我已經解雇你了  - 事實上 你沒做到 解雇我
That's enough. I think we get it.
夠了 我們明白了
- Yeah?  - Mr Bingham, I'm here to inform you your position is no longer available.
- 是嗎?  - Bingham先生 我來是通知你 你的職位已經不需要人手了
- I'm fired?  - Yes, you're fired.
- 我被炒魷魚了?  - 是的 你被炒魷魚了
- Never say fired.  - You've been let go.
- 永遠別說炒魷魚  - 你可以走了
Why?
為什麼?
This is a mythical situation. How could I possibly know why?
這是個虛擬場景 我怎麼可能知道為什麼?
Why doesn't matter, you never know why.
為什麼不重要 你永遠不會知道為什麼
Don't focus on the why. Rather, spend your energy thinking about your future.
別老想著為什麼 不如 把精力花在規劃未來上
Well, I'm gonna spend my energy on suing you
呃 我要花精力起訴你
unless you give me a good reason why you're firing me.
除非你給我一個解雇我的合理解釋
Mr. Bingham, the reason's not important.
Bingham先生 原因並不重要
You're firing me without grounds? Now I really have a lawsuit.
你毫無緣由的解雇我? 現在我真要起訴了
- I get what you're trying to say, Ryan.  - Don't take this personally, Mr. Bingham.
- 我知道你想說什麼了 Ryan  - 這不是針對你個人的 Bingham先生
Personally?
個人?
This is the most personal situation you are ever gonna enter,
這是你將要遇到的最個人的狀況
so before you try to revolutionise my business,
所以在你想改革我的工作之前
I'd like to know that you actually know my business.
我要知道 你確實瞭解我的工作
That's a hell of a way to welcome her to the team.
這樣歡迎她進組真糟糕
Am I the only one that sees that by doing this we're making ourselves irrelevant?
難道就我一人眼睜睜看著 這樣做讓我們把自己變得不相干了?
No, frankly, we're making you irrelevant.
不 老實說 我們把你變得不相干了
- Nice.  - Don't blame me.
- 真好  - 別怪我
Blame high fuel costs, blame insurance premiums, blame technology.
要怪就怪貴死的燃料 怪保險費 怪新科技
You're gonna watch yourself. You're a little too young to become a dinosaur.
你要注意 要變成老古董 你還太年輕
- I'm not a dinosaur.  - I want you to show her the ropes.
- 我不是老古董  - 我想讓你教教她
What do I know what goes on here? Get Ferguson to do it.
我哪知道要怎麼做? 讓Ferguson去做吧
I'm not talking about here.
我不是在這討論
- No.  - Yeah.
- 不  - 是的
You're very confident this girl doesn't know what she's doing. So...
你堅信那女孩不知道她自己在做什麼 所以...
I'm sorry. I don't think a MySpace page qualifies you to rewire a company.
很抱歉 我不覺得一個聚友的網頁就能讓你把整個公司聯繫起來
That's been great. Here's your chance. Go out, show her the magic, take her through the paces.
那好 你的機會來了 出去 給她露兩手 教教她做這行
I'm not a fucking tour guide.
我又不是他媽的導遊
- Now here we go.  - Bingham, here's the boat,
- 你又來了  - Bingham 這是船
and here's you. Do you want to be in the boat?
這是你 你想上船嗎?
Yeah, alone.
想 獨自一人
We're ringing the bell, we're rounding everybody up.
我們要開始革新了 要把大家都聚起來
You want to stay out a bit longer, you're welcome, but you will not be alone. Ok?
你想在外面待久一點 沒問題 但你不能一個人 好嗎?
You let me know.
想清楚 再跟我說
Oh, Christ.
噢 上帝
- What?  - Follow me.
- 怎麼了?  - 跟我來
- I really like my luggage.  - That's exactly what it is... luggage.
- 我很喜歡我的行李箱  - 對極了 這就是... 行李箱
Know how much time you lose checking in?
知道這樣登機要浪費多長時間嗎?
- I don't know. Five... ten minutes?  - 35 minutes a flight.
- 不知道 五... 十分鐘?  - 一個航班耽誤35分鐘
I travel 270 days a year. That's 157 hours.
我一年出差270天 那就有157個小時
That makes seven days. Are you willing to throw away an entire week on that?
相當於七天 你想把一整個星期浪費在這上面?
You don't need this. Sorry, you don't need that.
你不需要這個 抱歉 你不需要那個
You don't need that. They have neck pillows on the plane.
你不需要那個 飛機上有枕頭
This... they have better ones there. I'll get rid of this.
這個... 他們那的更好 我要把這個扔了
I can just meet you at security.
我們可以在安檢那兒見
Thank you.
謝謝
Bingo. Asians.
好的 亞洲人
- You can't be serious.  - Never get behind people with infants.
- 你不是認真的吧  - 永遠別排在帶小孩的大人後面
I've never seen a stroller collapse in less than 20 minutes.
我從沒見過有哪個推嬰兒車的 能在20分鐘內搞定
Old people are worse. Their bodies are littered with hidden metal
老人更糟 他們身上到處藏著金屬製品
and they never appreciate how little time they have left on earth.
時日無多 他們卻從不珍惜
Here we go. Five words: randomly selected for additional screening.
看他們 五字真言: 特檢幾率小
Asians, they pack light, travel efficiently,
亞洲人 他們行李輕便 有效率
and they've got a thing for slip-on shoes. Got a little.
而且他們穿容易脫的鞋 少花時間
- That's racist.  - I'm like my mother, I stereotype. It's faster.
- 這是種族歧視  - 我像我媽 看人有偏見 但我更快
Are you mad at your computer?
你跟你的電腦有仇嗎?
I type with purpose.
我正在做東西
What is it that you're working on so furiously?
你這麼猛烈地在做什麼?
I'm building a workflow of firing techniques.
我在建立解雇技術的工作流程
It's questions and responses, actions and reactions.
就是問題與應答 行為與反應
A script taking you through the steps of firing someone.
這個腳本給你提供裁員步驟
Who's it for?
為誰設計的?
Well, theoretically,
呃 理論上講
you could put it in the hands of anyone and they'd be downsizing immediately.
放之四海而皆准 可用於迅速裁員
All you have to do is follow the steps.
你只要按步驟來就行了
Natalie, what is it you think we do here?
Natalie 你覺得我們是幹什麼的?
We prepare the newly-unemployed for the emotional and physical hurdles of job hunting,
我們為剛被解雇的員工 處理再次求職遇到的身體及心理問題
while minimising legal blowback.
同時盡可能減少法律訴訟
That's what we're selling. It's not what we're doing.
那是我們對外說的 並非我們所做的
- OK, what are we doing?  - We are here to make limbo tolerable,
- 好吧 那我們是幹什麼的?  - 我們讓地獄不那麼可怕
to ferry wounded souls across the river of dread until the point where hope is dimly visible.
我們用渡船幫助受傷的魂靈渡過恐懼之河 直到希望之光隱約可見
Then stop the boat, shove 'em in the water and make 'em swim.
然後停下船 推他們下水 讓他們游泳
That's really impressive. Are you gonna put that in your book?
真精彩 你要把它寫到書裡嗎?
- I gotta grab this. I'll meet you at the car rental.  - Okay.
- 我要接下電話 在汽車出租公司見  - 好的
Hey, I was hoping I'd hear from you.
嘿 我一直等你的消息
I'm in Hotlanta and I need a rib-joint recommend bad.
我在特蘭大 給我推薦家肋排餐館吧
Fat Matt's. Bring a bib.
肥麥特餐館 帶上圍嘴
- You never called.  - I wasn't sure what was appropriate.
- 你一直沒打電話  - 我不知道那樣是否合適
Appropriate? Right, I'm not some waitress you banged in a snowstorm.
合適? 我不是你在大雪天搞上的女服務員
That word has no place in our vocabulary.
我們的字典裡沒有這個詞
I'm the woman that you don't have to worry about.
我是個不需要你擔心的女人
- Sounds like a trap.  - Listen...
- 聽起來是個陷阱  - 聽著...
the next time that you're worried about manners, don't.
以後別再擔心禮儀什麼的 不需要
If you wanna call, call. Just think of me as yourself, only with a vagina.
你想打電話 就打 把我當成你自己 就是多了個陰道
When am I gonna see you?
我要在哪見你?
Well, I'm out of Hartsfield into IAD, with a connection in ORD into SDF.
呃 我要離開Hartsfield去IAD機場 然後從ORD轉到SDF機場
Sorry.
真遺憾
Yeah, tell me about it.
對 你說的是
How long's your layover? They got multiples into SDF. Could you push?
你中間停留多久?  到SDF的航班很多 你能推遲點嗎?
Yeah, I can push.
可以 我可以推後點
All you have to do today is watch and listen.
你今天要做的就是看和聽
And when I talk about a strategy packet, hand them one of those.
當我說到策略文件包時 你就給他們一份
Sounds great.
聽起來不錯
So although I wish I were here with better news,
雖然我希望我能帶來好消息
the fact is that you and I are sitting here today because
但你和我坐在這兒是因為
this will be your last week of employment at this company.
這將是你在公司的最後一周了
- Why me?  - What am I supposed to do now?
- 為什麼是我?  - 我現在該怎麼辦?
Am I supposed to feel better I'm not the only one losing my job?
我是不是該慶幸我不是唯一被炒魷魚的?
This is ridiculous! I have been a fine employee for over 10 years
太荒謬了! 我在這兢兢業業十年多
and this is the way you treat me.
你們就這麼對我
How do you sleep at night, man? How?
你夜裡怎麼睡得著 夥計? 怎麼睡得著?
How's your family? They sleeping well at night?
你家人呢? 他們夜裡睡得好嗎?
Electricity still on?
電照樣通?
Heat still on, refrigerator full of food?
暖氣照樣通 冰箱照樣裝滿食物?
Gas tank full of gas?
煤氣罐照樣裝滿煤氣?
Going to Chuck E. Cheese this weekend or something?
週末還能去查克起司(餐廳名)什麼的?
Not me.
我就不行了
No, my kids, we're not gonna do anything.
不 我的孩子 我們什麼也做不了
What do you suggest I tell them?
你要我怎麼跟他們說?
Perhaps you're underestimating the positive effect
也許你低估了你職業轉變
your career transition can have on your children.
對你孩子的有利影響
The positive effect?
有利影響?
I make about 90 grand a year now.
我現在一年賺大概9萬美元
Unemployment is what... 250 bucks a week?
失業以後呢... 一星期250美元?
Is that one of your positive effects?
這就是你所謂的有利影響之一?
We'll get to be cosier cos I'm not gonna be able to pay my mortgage on my house.
我們會過得很難 因為我付不起房貸了
So maybe we can move into a nice fucking one-bedroom apartment somewhere.
所以我們可能要搬到某個漂亮的 該死的一居室公寓裡了
And I guess without benefits,
另外 我猜沒了工作
I'll be able to hold my daughter as she, you know, suffers from her asthma
她哮喘發作時 我就只能看著我的女兒
that I won't be able to afford the medication for.
因為我付不起醫療費了
Well... tests have shown that children under moderate trauma have a tendency to
呃... 測試顯示受中等創傷的孩子
apply themselves academically...
在學術上會更努力...
as a method of coping.
這是他們處理的方式
Go fuck yourself.
去你媽的
That's what my kids'll think.
那才是我孩子的想法
- Your children's admiration is important to you?  - Yeah.
- 孩子的崇拜對你很重要?  - 是的
Yeah, it was.
是的 確實是
Well, I doubt they ever admired you, Bob.
呃 我懷疑他們是否崇拜過你 Bob
Hey, asshole, aren't you supposed to be consoling me?
嘿 混蛋 你不是該安慰我嗎?
I'm not a shrink, Bob. I'm a wake-up call.
我不是心理醫生 Bob 我只是個叫醒電話
- You know why kids love athletes?  - Cos they screw lingerie models?
- 你知道孩子為什麼喜歡運動員嗎?  - 因為他們搞上了內衣模特?
No, that's why we love athletes. Kids love athletes
不 那是我們喜歡運動員的原因 孩子們喜歡
because they follow their dreams.
因為他們追逐夢想
- Well, I can't dunk.  - No, but you can cook.
- 呃 我不會灌籃  - 對 但你會做飯
What are you talking about?
你在說什麼?
Your resume says that you minored in French culinary arts.
簡歷上說你輔修過法國烹飪技術
Most students, they work on the fryer at KFC,
大多數學生 在肯德基準備油炸食品
but you bussed tables at Il Picador to support yourself.
而你卻在鬥牛士餐廳打工賺錢
Then you get out of college and then you come and work here.
然後你大學畢業 來到這工作
How much did they first pay you to give up on your dreams?
他們當時給你多少薪水 就讓你放棄了夢想?
- 27 grand a year.  - And when were you going to stop
- 一年兩萬七千美元  - 那你什麼時候才會停下來
and come back and do what makes you happy?
回過頭做讓你自己開心的事?
Good question.
好問題
I see guys who work at the same company for their entire lives,
我見過一些人 一輩子就待在一家公司
guys exactly like you.
就像你一樣
They clock in, they clock out, and they never have a moment of happiness.
他們上班 下班 從未有過片刻的喜悅
You have an opportunity here, Bob.
你現在有個機會 Bob
This is a rebirth.
這是一次重生
If not for you, do it for your children.
就算不為了你自己 也是為了你的孩子
He just waltzes in and cuts in line?
他就那樣大搖大擺地插隊?
We reserve priority assistance for our Hilton Honors members.
我們為希爾頓榮譽會員優先提供服務
The promotions are great. You should check it out.
會員制度非常棒 你應該來看看
Hungry much?
很餓嗎?
Our business expense allots $40 each for dinner.
咱們每頓的餐飲費預算是40美元
I plan on grabbing as many miles as I can.
我計劃盡可能的賺英里數
OK, you gotta fill me in on the miles thing. What is that about?
好吧 你來告訴我英里數的事情 那是關於什麼的?
Are you talking about... like frequent flyer miles?
你是不是在說... 飛行常客的英里數?
- You really want to know?  - I'm dying to know.
- 你真想知道?  - 我極其想知道
I don't spend a nickel if I can help it unless it somehow profits my mileage account.
如果不有益於我的英里數賬戶 我一個子兒也不會花的
So what are you saving up for... Hawaii, South of France?
你攢英里數為了... 去夏威夷 法國南部?
It's not like that. The miles are the goal.
並不是那樣 目標就是英里數
That's it?
就這樣?
You're saving just to save?
你攢英里數就是為了攢英里數?
Just say I have a number in mind and I haven't hit it yet.
我只是說我腦中有一個數字 我還沒達到而已
That's a little abstract. What's the target?
那有點抽像 目標是什麼?
- I'd rather not.  - Is it a secret target?
- 我不想說  - 是秘密?
It's 10 million miles.
一千萬英里
- OK. Isn't 10 million just a number?  - Pi's just a number.
- 好吧 一千萬不就是個數字嘛?  - π也就是個數字
Well, we all need a hobby.
呃 我們都得有點嗜好
No, I... I don't mean to belittle your collection. I get it. It sounds cool.
不 我... 我不是有意貶低你的愛好 我明白了 那很酷
I'd be the seventh person to do it. More people have walked on the moon.
我會是第7個做到的人 上過月球的人都比這多
- Do they throw you a parade?  - You get lifetime executive status,
- 他們給你來了個遊行慶祝?  - 你有終生的行政地位
you get to meet the chief pilot, Maynard Finch...
你能見到機長 Maynard Finch...
And they put your name on a plane.
而且 他們把你的名字寫在飛機上
Men get hard-ons putting their name on stuff. You guys don't grow up.
男人總是渴望自己名字出現在某些東西上 你們都還沒長大
- It's like you need to pee on everything.  - Now who's stereotyping?
- 就像你們隨處小便一樣  - 現在是誰有偏見啊?
Fear of mortality. It's like, yeah, you're gonna die one day.
是對死亡的恐懼 就像是 你某天會死去
Why do you suppose that's singular to men?
你為什麼覺得只有男人會這麼想?
- Probably because you can't have babies.  - The baby argument.
- 很可能因為你們不能生孩子  - 孩子理論
If I had that many miles...
如果我有那麼多英里數...
I would show up at an airport,
我就在機場炫耀
look at the destination board, pick a place and go.
看著指路牌 選個地方 然後就去
Thanks for the advice.
多謝你的建議
Have sweet dreams about me.
那就做個裡面有我的春夢吧
OK. Closer. Way closer.
好的 向前 再向前點
Still closer.
再往前
Closer.
往前
Er... a little left.
呃... 稍向左
Down a little.
往下點
Too far. Up. Up one more inch.
下去太多了 往上 再往上一英吋
I don't get it. Why does your sister want a fake photo?
我不明白 為什麼你妹妹會想要張假照片?
My sister is kooky. She thinks this is charming. It's like the Gnome Thing.
我妹妹很奇怪的 她覺得這很有趣 就像地精一樣
No, I mean, why would she want a fake photo in front of St Louis airport?
不 我想問的是 她為什麼會想要一張在聖路易機場的照片?
Are you kidding... Lambert Field? The Wright brothers flew through there.
你在開玩笑嗎... 這可是Lambert機場呀 懷特兄弟飛越過這裡
That domed main terminal,
主航站樓的那個屋頂
is the first of its kind, a precursor of everything from JFK to de Gaulle.
是圓屋頂的首創 肯尼迪和戴高樂機場 都是按照它的設計理念設計的
- Pretty sweet.  - Just take the picture.
- 真厲害  - 照你的相
Well, that's a keeper.
好了 照下來了
Let me see it.
讓我看看
Why she wants reminders of all the places she hasn't been is beyond me. But...
我也不知道她為什麼 要在這些她從沒去過的地方留念 但是...
I'm sure she'll be crushed for having missed this airport.
我相信她沒能來這兒一定很痛苦
Look, before Lindbergh crossed the Atlantic, he took off from one of those runways.
在Lindbergh飛越大西洋之前 他曾經從這裡的某條跑道上起飛
Do you ever wonder why they called it the Spirit of St Louis?
你從沒好奇過 為什麼人們稱之為聖路易精神麼?
- No.  - Well...
- 沒有  - 好吧...
Do you know how fucked this place is now?
你知道這該死的公司變成什麼樣了嗎?
I am the one thing... the one thing...
我是那個... 那個...
preventing this place from being totally fucked in the ass.
讓公司不再一團糟的人
Sometimes they just need to vent.
他們有時候需要發洩一下
Please, for the love of God, can I fire the next one?
拜託 看在上帝的份上 下一個能不能讓我開除?
- Miss Barnes, thank you for joining us.  - I'm here to be fired, right?
- Barnes小姐 謝謝你參加  - 我要被開除了 是嗎?
Well, we're here to talk about your future.
我們是想和您談談您以後的計劃
You don't have to sugar-coat it. I get the drill.
你不用說什麼好聽的 我明白你們想說什麼
What are they offering?
他們會給我什麼?
Inside the packet, you'll find a clearly worked out severance package.
在文件夾裡 你可以看到一個明晰的遣散費條款
Give me the bullet points.
直接告訴我重點
It's actually pretty good...
其實條件很優厚...
three months' pay, six months' medical.
三個月的工資 六個月的醫療保險
And a full year of placement services through our company CTC.
還有由我們公司付款一年的就業咨詢服務
Placement services. That's generous.
求職咨詢 真是慷慨啊
Commonly it takes a month of searching for every $10,000 you expect to earn in salary.
一般的話 想找到一份年薪一萬的工作只需要一個月的時間
- So I could be looking for a while.  - Not necessarily.
- 這樣說來我可以再等等看了  - 也不是這麼說
Don't even sweat it. I'm pretty confident about my plans.
不要緊張 我對自己的計劃還是很有信心的
- Really?  - Yeah.
- 真的?  - 對
There's this beautiful bridge by my house.
我家旁邊有一座很美麗的大橋
I'm gonna go jump off it.
我要從上面跳下去
Natalie.
Natalie啊
Hey!
嘿!
Natalie!
Natalie啊!
People say these things all the time. It's part of the trade.
人們總是這樣子說話的 這就是我們的工作
- They do?  - Yeah.
- 真的?  - 對
They say crazy things. They get worked up.
他們會說很難聽的話 他們會變得非常易怒
She was really calm.
她看起來很平靜的
I think that's a good sign.
我覺得那是個很好的信號
- So they don't ever actually do it?  - No. No, it's just talk.
- 所以他們其實並不會真的那麼做?  - 不會 只是說說而已
- How do you know? Do you follow up?  - I mean, no, nothing good's gonna come of that, but..
- 你怎麼知道? 你跟蹤調查過?  - 沒有 這種事當然沒什麼好結果 但是...
I wouldn't worry about it.
我不會去操這種心
This is what we do, Natalie. We take people at their most fragile and we set them adrift.
這就是我們的工作 Natalie 我們讓人們在他們最脆弱的時候失去了依靠
Ready to go back in?
準備好繼續了嗎?
All right, let's go. Come on.
好的 走吧 來
No, I'm fine. Tell me something sweet.
不 我很好 告訴我些開心的事吧
I'll be back soon. I'm not sure how long this exercise is supposed to last.
我很快就可以回去了 我也不知道實習會持續多久
No, I don't even think of him that way. He's old.
不 我才沒想過那方面的事呢 他那麼老
- I... I'm done?  - I wasn't expecting this. Not at all.
- 我... 我被開除了?  - 我壓根沒想到 一點兒都沒有
Just like that?
就這樣?
I'm disappointed that I've given so much of my life...
我很失望 我付出了我生命中那麼多的...
This is not fair.
這不公平
There are people who gonna be way more qualified than me now.
現在有那麼多比我更適合這個職位的人
I don't know what to do when I wake up in the morning, tomorrow.
我不知道明天早上起床後 要做什麼了
You OK?
你還好嗎?
- Are we going?  - Yeah.
- 我們要走了?  - 對
This is how I start every day of my life.
我每天就是這麼開始的
Now, this is gonna be a little difficult, so stay with me.
現在 可能會有一點困難 所以 跟著我的思路
You have a new backpack.
你有一個新背包
Only this time, I want you to fill it with people.
只是這次 我要你把它裝滿人
Start with casual acquaintances, friends of friends,
從泛泛之交開始 到朋友的朋友
folks around the office.
再到公司的同事
And then the people you trust with your most intimate secrets...
再到那些你相信 並願意和他們分享你內心秘密的人...
your cousins, your aunts, your uncles,
你的堂兄妹 你的姑姑阿姨 你的叔叔舅舅
your brothers, your sisters, your parents,
你的兄弟 你的姐妹 你的父母親
and finally your husband, your wife, your boyfriend or your girlfriend.
最後到了你的丈夫 你的老婆 你的男朋友 或是你的女朋友
You get them into that backpack.
你要把他們都裝進那個背包裡去
Don't worry. I'm not gonna ask you to light it on fire.
別著急 我不會讓你們一把火燒掉的
Feel the weight of that bag.
感受那個背包的重量
Make no mistake, your relationships are the heaviest components in your life.
不能犯錯 你的人際關係是你人生中最重要的部分
Do you feel the straps cutting into your shoulders?
感受到陷進你肩膀裡的帶子的壓力了嗎?
All those negotiations and arguments, and secrets and compromises.
所有的談判和爭執 所有的秘密和妥協
You don't need to carry all that weight.
其實你不需要承受那麼多重量的
Why don't you set that bag down?
為什麼不放下那背包呢?
Some animals were meant to carry each other, to live symbiotically for a lifetime...
有些動物生來就是為了互相扶持 一輩子都要生活在一起...
star-crossed lovers, monogamous swans. We are not those animals.
時運不濟的戀人 終生一夫一妻制的天鵝 我們不是那些動物
The slower we move, the faster we die.
我們運動得越慢 死得越快
We are not swans.
我們不是天鵝
We're sharks.
我們是鯊魚
- Never?  - No.
- 永遠不會?  - 不會
- Ever?  - No.
- 從來沒有?  - 沒有
- You never want to get married?  - Nope.
- 你從來沒想過要結婚?  - 沒
- Never want kids?  - Not a chance.
- 沒想要孩子?  - 一次都沒有
- Ever?  - Never.
- 從來?  - 從來沒有
- Is that so bizarre?  - Yes.
- 很奇怪嗎?  - 是
- Yes, it is.  - I just don't see the value in it.
- 對 很奇怪  - 我只是沒發現那樣做的意義
- Right, sell it to me.  - What?
- 好吧 推銷給我  - 什麼?
Sell me marriage.
把婚姻推銷給我
- OK, how about love?  - OK.
- 好吧 愛不會讓你想結婚嗎?  - 好吧
- Stability, just somebody you can count on...  - How many stable marriages do you know?
- 穩定 就是你可以依靠某人...  - 你知道有多少穩定的婚姻嗎?
Somebody to talk to, someone to spend your life with.
可以和某人說話 可以和某人共度一生
I'm surrounded by people to talk to. I doubt that's not gonna change.
我周圍全是可以說話的人 我覺得那是不會變的
How about just not dying alone?
為了不會一個人死去?
Starting when I was 12, we moved each of my grandparents to a nursing facility.
從我12歲開始 我們就開始把我的祖父母送去養老院
My parents went the same way. Make no mistake, we all die alone.
我的父母也去了養老院 如果沒說錯的話 我們都會一個人死去的
Now, those cult members in San Diego, with the Kool-Aid and the sneakers...
不過 那些在聖地亞哥喝著最愛的飲料 穿著運動鞋的邪教份子...
they didn't die alone.
倒不會一個人死去
I'm just saying there are options.
我只是說還有不同的選擇
Oh, fuck.
我靠
Brian left me.
Brian拋棄我了
All right.
沒事了
OK. Ok. All right.
好 好 沒事了
All right. Shh, shh.
沒事了 噓 噓
Hey.
嘿
Natalie, this is Alex, my friend. This is Natalie.
Natalie 這是我朋友Alex 這是Natalie
I should give you both a moment.
我應該迴避一下嗎?
No. No, that's fine. I'm fine. It's a pleasure to meet you.
不 不 沒關係的 我沒事 很高興見到你
Maybe we should just all go up to our rooms and freshen up.
也許我們應該回房間去洗把臉
- Maybe a drink?  - Now you're talking.
- 或是喝一杯?  - 就按你說的
Brian: I think it's time we C other people
Brian: 我覺得我們該分手了
He broke up with you with a text message?
他就用短信和你分手?
Kind of like firing someone over the internet.
就像是通過網絡解雇別人一樣
- What a weaselly prick.  - But what does that make me?
- 多狡猾的賤人  - 那我是啥?
- Someone who falls for a prick.  - We all fall for them.
- 愛上賤人的傻瓜  - 我們都會愛上他們的
Pricks are spontaneous, unpredictable and fun.
賤人會很隨意 不可捉摸 很有趣
Then we're surprised when they turn out to be pricks.
然後我們會很驚訝 原來他們那麼無恥
- I followed him to Omaha.  - You did?
- 我是為了他來的奧馬哈  - 真的?
I had a job waiting for me in San Francisco when he got an offer from ConAgra.
我本來在舊金山有一份工作的 但是他接到了康尼格拉(美國食品公司)的錄用通知
He said we could start a life together.
他說我們可以一起開創新生活
- So I followed him.  - To Nebraska?
- 所以我跟著他  - 到了內布拉斯加?
I thought I'd be engaged by now.
我以為我們會訂婚的
No offence.
不要見怪
- None taken.  - That's all right.
- 沒發現  - 沒關係
When I was 16, I thought by 23 I'd be married,
當我16歲的時候 我覺得我23歲就會結婚
maybe have a kid, corner office by day, entertaining at night.
會有一個小孩 白天坐在辦公室角落 晚上出去玩
I was supposed to be driving a Grand Cherokee by now.
我應該開著切諾基上班的
Life can underwhelm you that way.
生活有時候會讓你失望的
I mean, where did you think you'd be by um...
我是說 你怎麼知道你會在哪裡被...
- It doesn't work that way.  - At a certain point, you stop with the deadlines.
- 事實不總按著你的想法走的  – 在某處 你設定個截止期限
It can be counterproductive.
有時候反而會適得其反
I don't want to say anything anti-feminist.
我不是反對男女平等
I really appreciate all your generation did for me.
我很感激你們那一代人為我們女人做的一切
- It was our pleasure.  - Well done.
- 是我們的榮幸  - 做得很不錯
But sometimes it feels like, no matter how much success I have,
但是有時候我感覺 不論我有多成功
it's not gonna matter until I find the right guy.
除非我找到了命中注定的那位 一切都不重要
You really thought this guy was the one?
你真的覺得這個人就是那位嗎?
I could have made it work.
我本可以實現的
He um... he really fit the bill.
他 呃... 他符合我的要求
- You know?  - The bill?
- 你知道嗎?  - 你的要求?
White collar, college grad.
白領階層 大學學歷
Loves dogs, likes funny movies. Six-foot-one, brown hair, kind eyes,
喜歡小狗 喜歡喜劇 1米8的個子 褐色頭髮 迷人的雙眼
works in finance but is outdoorsy... you know, on the weekends.
專業是金融 但喜愛戶外運動... 在週末
I always imagined he'd have a single syllable name like Matt or John...
我希望他有一個字的名字 像是Matt 或是John...
or Dave.
或是Dave
In a perfect world, he drives a 4Runner, and
在理想的世界中 他開著豐田的4Runner
and the only thing he loves more than me is his golden lab.
他愛他的黃金實驗室勝過愛我
And a nice smile.
還要有可愛的笑容
- What about you?  - Let me think.
- 你呢?  - 讓我想想
Honestly, by the time you're 34, all the physical requirements just go out the window.
實話說 當你34歲的時候 所有的身體條件已經不重要了
Like you secretly pray that he'll be taller than you.
比如你默默祈求他比你高
Not an asshole would be nice. Someone who enjoys my company, comes from a good family.
他不是個混蛋就好了 他喜歡我的陪伴 他有個良好的家庭
You don't think about that when you're younger.
你年輕的時候 不會想這些的
I don't know... someone who wants kids.
我不知道... 他還應該想要孩子
Likes kids. Wants kids
喜歡小孩 想要小孩
Healthy enough to play with his kids.
身體健康 可以和孩子們一起玩
Please let him earn more money than I do.
上帝拜託讓他比我掙得比我多吧
You might not understand that now, but believe me, you will one day.
你可能現在不能瞭解 但相信我 總有一天你會瞭解的
Otherwise that's a recipe for disaster.
不然的話 那肯定就是一個災難了
And hopefully some hair on his head.
而且希望他沒有謝頂
But I mean even that's not a deal breaker these days.
但是現在那也不是決定性因素了
A nice smile.
一個可愛的笑容
Yeah, a nice smile. Nice smile just might do it.
對 一個可愛的笑容 可愛的笑容很重要
Wow, that was depressing.
哇 那真傷感
- I should just date women.  - Tried it.
- 我應該和女人約會了  - 我試過了
We're no picnic ourselves.
我們一個人過不去的
I don't mind being married to my career.
我一點都不介意嫁給我的事業
And I don't expect it to hold me in bed as I fall asleep.
我也不指望 它在我睡覺的時候抱著我
I just don't want to settle.
我只是不想安頓下來
You're young. Right now you see settling as some sort of a failure.
你還年輕 現在你認為安頓意味著失敗
It is... by definition.
那是... 我的定義
But by the time someone is right for you, it won't feel like settling.
但是當你遇到對的人 你不會想要安頓
And the only person left to judge you
那麼唯一可以評判你的人
will be the 23-year-old girl with a target on your back.
就是你身後那個有明確目標的23歲女孩
So what's the plan for the evening?
晚上有什麼計劃?
Well, we were gonna hit that party for the tech conference at the hotel.
我們本想去參加飯店裡 那個科技會議舉行的派對
I didn't know you could just attend those. I thought you had to register.
我不知道你們也能參加 我以為必須要登記的
Technically, I don't think it's open to the public.
理論上說 那個派對不對外開放的
- Stop by.  - You're gonna crash it?
- 被攔下來  - 你們要闖進去?
- have a good time, usually. - No, no, I get it. I'm in.
- 通常會很好玩  - 不 我明白 我也要參加
Jennifer Chu?
Jennifer Chu?
- Shit!  - Ah, it'll be fine.
- 靠!  - 啊 沒關係的
Doing all right?
一切還好?
Yeah. This was a great idea.
是 這真是個好主意
You're so pretty.
你真漂亮
You're exactly what I wanna look like in 15 years.
我多希望自己15年後可以像你這樣漂亮
- Thank you, Natalie.  - You should dance.
- 謝謝 Natalie  - 你應該跳舞
- Come on.  - No, no, no.
- 來吧  - 不 不 不
- Come on.  - Oh!
- 來吧  - 噢!
- I'm Dave.  - I'm Natalie.
- 我是Dave  - 我是Natalie
Who's Jennifer?
那Jennifer是誰?
I don't know.
不知道
How's everybody doing out there?
大家開心嗎?
Right about now, give it up for a very special alphaTECH guest.
現在 讓我們熱烈歡迎alphaTECH的特邀嘉賓
Young MC!
Young MC!
What's up, alphaTECH?
怎麼樣 alphaTECH?
I got a busted computer. Can somebody fix it for me?
我電腦最近壞了 有人能幫我修修嗎？
I want you to have a key to my place.
我希望你能拿著我房間的鑰匙
Wow. I had no idea we were at that point in our relationship.
哇 我都不知道我們之間已經到了這個地步了
- Oh, yes.  - Wow.
- 當然有  - 哇
Where is she?
她在哪兒?
# Lyin' in my bed I hear the clock tick and think of you #
# 我躺在床上 聽著鐘錶滴答 想起了你 #
# Caught up in circles, confusion is nothing new #
# 陷在回憶中 我無比困惑 #
# Flash back Warm night Almost left behind #
# 回憶浮現 溫暖的夜晚 幾乎就要忘卻 #
# Suitcase Memories Time after some time #
# 箱子 記憶 不停的出現 #
Back home I don't get to act the way I do with you.
回到家後 我就不會像現在和你一起時這樣了
- That's why I don't have a back home.  - I know.
- 這就是我為什麼不回家的原因  - 我發現了
You're so cool. Mr Empty Backpack.
你真冷漠 空包先生
- You know about my backpack?  - I Googled you.
- 你知道我的背包理論?  - 我在Google上搜了一下
You did?
真的?
It's what us modern girls do when we have a crush.
如今女生迷戀男生都會這樣
- Does it bother you?  - It depends.
- 你不喜歡嗎?  - 看情況了
Is the bag empty because you hate people or because you hate the baggage they come along with?
你要把背包清空 是因為討厭人呢 還是討厭他們的背包?
I don't hate people. I'm not exactly a hermit.
我不討厭和人相處 我不能算一個隱士吧
You just don't want to be tied down with the whole responsibility thing.
你只是不想被那麼多的責任所束縛
I don't know what originally sparked the backpack.
我不知道最初是什麼啟發我的空包思考
Probably needed to be alone.
也許是因為我需要獨處
Recently, I've been thinking that I needed to empty the backpack
最近 我一直在想 在我知道應該把什麼放進之前
before I know what to put back in it.
應該先把它清空
- Oh, no!  - I think we're out of gas.
- 哦 不!  - 我想是汽油用完了
Hey. You're up?
嘿 你起來了?
I have to fly standby and make a meeting in Cincinnati.
我要飛去辛辛那提去開個會
OK.
好吧
I made you feel cheap.
我傷你自尊了
It's all right. Just leave the money on the dresser.
沒關係 把錢放化妝台就行了
I'll text you later so we can swap schedules.
過會兒我給你發短信 我們交換下行程表
Hey.
嘿
I really like you.
我真的很喜歡你
- I like you too.  - Good.
- 我也喜歡你  - 真好
Go catch your plane.
去趕飛機吧
Last night er...
昨晚 呃...
It was kind of out of hand. I said things, erm...
我有點失控 說的話...
I'm not actually sure everything that I said.
我也不確定自己說了什麼
- But I didn't want you to think...  - Just relax.
- 但請你不要認為...  - 沒事
It was nice to see you cut loose.
看到你放鬆自我 我很高興
Did you wake him up or slip out?
你叫醒他 還是溜出來的?
- What?  - This morning. Your new friend.
- 什麼?  - 今天早上 你的新朋友
Did you wake him up for an awkward goodbye, or did you
你叫醒他 尷尬的說聲再見 還是
just slip out and make him feel like a whore?
偷偷溜出來 像個妓女?
- I just left.  - Protocol's always tricky.
- 我就那麼走了  - 社交禮儀總是很麻煩
What happened to Alex?
那Alex呢?
She had to leave town early to get to a meeting.
她一早就出城了 趕著開會
- That's too bad. Where's she live?  - Chicago.
- 真掃興 她住哪?  - 芝加哥
Thinking of going to see her?
想去見她嗎?
We don't really have that kind of relationship. Try it over there.
我們關係沒到那步 站那邊試試
What erm... kind of relationship do you have?
那 呃... 你們是什麼關係?
Well, you know... casual.
就是那種... 很隨意的
- Sounds pretty special.  - It works for us.
- 聽起來蠻特別的  - 挺適合我們的
Don't you think there's a future there?
沒想過你們會有未來嗎?
I never really thought about it. What's going on here?
我從來沒想過 問這個幹嗎?
- Really never thought about it?  - No.
- 真的從沒想過?  - 從沒
How can you not think about that?
你居然從沒想過你們的未來?
How does it not even cross your mind that you might want a future with someone?
你腦子就沒閃現過 和某人共度餘生的念頭?
It's simple. You know that moment when you look into somebody's eyes and you can
很簡單 當你看著某人的眼睛
feel them staring into your soul and the whole world goes quiet just for a second?
直觸靈魂 全世界在那一刻靜止?
- Yes.  - Right. Well, I don't.
- 知道  - 是吧 可我沒那感覺
You're an asshole.
你個混蛋
You know, look, I'm just dicking around. Come on, give me a hand.
我只是消磨時間 快點 幫我拍完
Dont't you think it's worth giving her a chance?
那你為什麼不給她一個機會?
- A chance for what?  - A chance at something real.
- 什麼機會?  - 付出真感情的機會
Natalie, your definition of real will evolve as you get older.
Natalie 對於"真感情"的理解 會隨著年齡的增長改變
Can you stop condescending for one second or is that one of the principles of your bullshit philosophy?
你能不能屈尊一下 還是那就是你那狗屁理論的原則?
- Bullshit philosophy?  - The isolation, the travelling.
- 狗屁理論?  - 什麼獨身 旅行
- Is that supposed to be charming?  - No, simply a life choice.
- 那樣很有魅力嗎?  - 不 只是種生活方式
- It's a cocoon of self-banishment.  - Wow. Big words.
- 那是自我放縱的借口  - 哇 過獎了
- Screw you.  - Screw you, too.
- 去你的  - 也去你的
You have set up a way of life that basically
你的生活方式基本上
makes it impossible for you to have any kind of human connection.
基本上隔絕了人際交往
And now this woman comes along and somehow runs the gauntlet of your ridiculous
現在有個女人出現 經歷你那荒謬的生活方式的鞭打
life choice, and comes out on the other end smiling just so you can call her "casual"?
還對你微笑 你卻說她"隨意"?
I need to grow up? You're a 12-year-old.
我需要長大成熟? 你才是12歲的小朋友
I don't have a gauntlet...
我沒有鞭打...
Fuck.
我靠
Listen, these Detroit guys can be tough. They're getting hammered.
聽著 這些底特律傢伙不好對付 他們是老油條了
So you don't get distracted. Stick with the simple stuff.
別分心 把簡單的事做好
Get these packets in their hands and get them out the door, OK?
把資料給他們 請他們走人 明白嗎?
Hey, welcome to Detroit.
嘿 歡迎來底特律
What's going on here?
怎麼回事?
I've been looking at those great numbers on last few days.
前幾天我一直注意那些大生意
I thought maybe we should just nut up and give this a try.
覺得我們應該大膽點 試試這種方式
We use a little more time.
我們需要多點時間
Well, you gotta leave the nest at some point, huh?
萬事都有個開頭 對吧?
This is a real company, Craig. We're here to do some damage.
這可是真正的公司 Craig 我們是來拆台的
I know. It's a good thing we brought our best, okay? Let's stop screwing around.
我知道 但有你們兩位精英 還怕什麼? 開始吧
Just give me a minute to prepare and get my things together.
給我一分鐘做準備
I was thinking Natalie was gonna take this one.
這次讓Natalie來吧
She's hardly ready for that.
恐怕她還不能勝任吧
I've been watched her results the last few days. She's great.
最近我一直關注她的工作成績 她很棒
This is a whole other animal.
這次和以前的任務完全不同啊
You know, she created it and everything right? Natalie, are you nut up for it?
這種方式就是她創造的 對吧? Natalie你準備好了嗎?
Yeah, I'm game.
沒問題
That's my girl.
看你的表現
Just remember, don't apologize or tell them how hard this is for you.
記住了 千萬別道歉 也別說自己也很為難
Today's one of the worst days they're ever gonna have in their life.
今天將是他們 一生中最鬱悶的一天
How we feel doesn't even compare.
我們的同情太微不足道了
- Got it.  - Just keep it professional. You'll be fine.
- 瞭解  - 專業點 沒事的
What's all this? What's going on?
這是幹什麼? 發生什麼事了?
Hello, Mr Samuels.
您好啊 Samuels先生
I wish I were here with better news.
我也希望自己帶給您的是好消息
However, your position here at Wall Timer's is no longer available.
但是 您在Wall Timer公司的職位保不住了
What are you talking about?
什麼意思?
You've been let go.
您被解雇了
Just like that?
就這麼簡單?
Who are you?
你是誰啊?
My name is Miss Keener and I'm here today to talk about your options.
我是Keener女士 今天是來和您談條件的
I worked for this company for 17 years and they send a 4th-grader to can me?
我為這個公司干了17年 他們就派個本科畢業生開了我?
What the fuck is this?
這他媽的太過分了?
It's perfectly normal to be upset.
您會這麼生氣 我很理解
However, the sooner you can tell yourself the greater opportunities are waiting for you.
不過 您盡早接受事實 就能盡快找到更好的工作機會
Greater opportunities? I'm 57 fucking years old.
更好的工作機會? 我他媽的都57歲了
Anybody who ever built an empire or changed the world sat where you are now.
那些曾建立帝國 改變世界的偉人們 也有過你這樣的遭遇
And it's because they sat there that they were able to do it.
也正因為他們經歷過 他們才能做到
There's a packet in front of you. I want you to take some time and review it.
您面前有份資料 希望您花時間讀下
All the answers you're looking for are inside those pages.
您的問題 資料裡都有答案
The sooner you trust the process,
你越早接受現實
the sooner the next step of your life will unveil itself.
您才能盡快開始新生活
I need you to go back to your office now and start putting together your personal things.
現在請您回辦公室 收拾自己的個人物品
Mr Samuels, that's all we can discuss now.
Samuels先生 我們的談話結束了
Mr Samuels.
Samuels先生
Mr Samuels!
Samuels先生!
You did good.
表現得不錯啊
You oK? You want me to take over?
你還好吧? 要我接手嗎?
No, I'm all right.
不用了 我沒事
Look, we just got here. That's one place. I think we need to try a few more.
我們剛到這 這只是開始 我認為得多試幾個
Maybe it doesn't make difference,
或許沒什麼區別
but it's comforting to know that we're in the next room.
但讓他們知道 我們就坐在隔壁 起碼有點安撫作用
I know you don't give a shit about my comfort.
我知道你才不管什麼安撫
I think we could try a few more, that's all I'm saying.
我就是想說 得多試幾個
Fine.
好吧
All right. OK. All right.
沒事 好的 沒事
He thought you did a great job. You did.
他說你表現很棒 確實是
- I'm real proud of you.  - Thanks.
- 我為你驕傲  - 謝謝
They're pulling us off the road.
他們想讓我們回去
We're going home.
我們要回家了
- Really? For good?  - Yeah.
- 真的? 不再回來了?  - 是啊
Good job.
做得不錯
I'm sorry about what I said about Alex. That was out of line.
關於Alex的那些話 我很抱歉 有點過分了
It's all right. I understand.
沒事 我理解
I mean, who am I to be doling out relationship advice, right?
我是誰啊 還給你提戀愛建議?
No kidding.
別開玩笑了
Are you gonna be oK?
你沒事嗎?
- What do you mean?  - In Omaha?
- 什麼意思?  - 在奧馬哈?
I don't know.
我也不知道
It's better than you'd think.
比你想像得好
Ryan.
Ryan
- Ryan. Where are you going?  - I'm grabbing another flight.
- Ryan 你去哪?  - 我搭另一班飛機
Something I've got to take care of. I'll see you back at home.
有點事要處理 回家見
OK, just walk it in a little.
好的 走近一點
A little more.
再近點
There you go. Yeah.
很好
Got it.
搞定
They're a cute couple.
他們真可愛
- You think so?  - Yeah, they'll make cute kids.
- 你這麼認為?  - 是啊 他們的孩子一定漂亮
How do you like Wisconsin in February?
你覺得二月去威斯康辛州怎樣?
I like it if you're there. I know a killer burger in Milwaukee.
你在那我就喜歡 我知道 密爾瓦基市有家很棒的漢堡店
Northern Wisconsin.
北威斯康辛州
What are you doing this weekend?
這週末有安排嗎?
- No.  - What, I haven't...
- 不會吧  - 什麼 我還沒...
- You want me to be your date?  - Yeah. Yeah.
- 你要我做你的約會對像?  - 是啊 是啊
- At your sister's wedding?  - It's not like I know her that well.
- 參加你妹妹的婚禮?  - 我和她的關係沒那麼親
Look, I'm not the wedding type, right?
我不是那種結婚型的 好嗎?
But for the first time in my life I don't want to be that guy alone at a bar.
但有生以來第一次 我不想獨自一人坐在酒吧裡
I want a dance partner, I want a "plus one".
我想有個舞伴 想要個"另一伴"
And if you can stomach it, I'd like it to be you.
如果你能接受的話 我希望那個人是你
Excuse me. Are you available?
打攪下 你有空嗎?
This line's for members of our Matterhorn Programme.
這邊只對參加"馬特洪峰計劃"的會員開放
Hey... Ryan.
嘿... Ryan
- Hey.  - Kara. Hi.
- 嘿  - Kara 嗨
- Alex, this is my sister Kara.  - Hi.
- Alex 這是我姐姐Kara  - 嗨
Well, hello.
你好啊
Ryan's told me nothing about you.
Ryan從來沒和我提過你
So you two are dating?
你們倆在約會嗎?
- Not exactly.  - Well, hey, don't worry about it.
- 不算吧  - 嘿 不用擔心
We're all getting a little old to be calling someone girlfriend.
我們這個年齡還叫對方女朋友有點過了
I remember when mom used to call Jack her boyfriend. God.
我還記得 媽媽說Jack是她男朋友 上帝啊
Drove me up the wall. Boyfriends are for kids, right?
讓我撞牆算了 小孩們才叫男朋友 對吧?
So what are you doing at the hotel?
你在旅館幹嗎呢?
Yeah, oK, er... Frank and I are trying out a trial separation.
呃... 我和Frank正試著分居
- I'm sorry. So you're not staying at the house?  - No, there was a room on hold here,
- 抱歉 那麼你不在家住了?  - 不住了 旅館有個房間
so I thought I'd just take it for the weekend.
所以我週末就過來住
- So the rehearsal dinner?  - Oh, yeah, tonight. I'll see you two there.
- 婚前晚宴什麼時候?  - 哦 對 就今晚 到時候見
Nice digs.
房間不錯嘛
There's a packet.
一本宣傳冊
Hey, look who's here.
嘿 快看誰來了
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Ryan!  - Hey.
- 哦 天那! 哦 天那! Ryan!  - 嘿
- Oh, you must be Alex.  - Yes, I am. Hi. How are you?
- 哦 你一定是Alex嘍  - 是啊 嗨 你好?
You are so beautiful. Kara was right.
你真漂亮 Kara說的沒錯
Gosh. You look so grown-up.
老天 你好成熟啊
I do? You're the one that's getting married.
我嗎? 可是快結婚的人是你啊
Oh, I know, right?
哦 沒錯?
Oh. You haven't even seen my ring.
哦 你們還沒看我的戒指呢
- Oh, look at that.  - Oh, it's lovely.
- 哦 快看啊  - 哦 真精緻
Jim designed it.
Jim設計的
Hey, Jim.
嘿 Jim
- Hey.  - How's it going?
- 嘿  - 過得怎樣?
- Hey. I'm Ryan.  - Jim. Good to meet you.
- 嘿 我是Ryan  - Jim 見到你很高興
- Alex.  - Pleasure.
- Alex  - 很榮幸
Pleasure.
很榮幸
Thank you, guys, for coming.
謝謝你們的到來
Brother!
哥!
- It's true, though.  - Yeah, it's crazy.
- 真的哦  - 是啊 瘋狂
- I got the pictures you asked me to get.  - You can just put them right there.
- 我把你們要的照片帶來了  - 貼那裡就行了
Yeah, oK.
好的
You got so many up there, I almost didn't have room.
那裡貼了好多啊  差點找不到地方
I know. It's so great, everyone just chipped in.
是啊 很棒吧 大家都幫忙了
What gave you the idea to do something so...
從哪來的靈感 這個主意好...
- Substantial.  - Well...
- 有意義  - 呃...
Jim has a lot of our nest egg invested in this real estate venture.
Jim 把我們大部分存款都投在了 房地產生意上
Mm-hm. It's a real estate investment.
嗯 房產投資
It's exciting, but we went over our finances and...
很興奮 但是我們算了一下帳發現...
A honeymoon just called, at this state in the game,
蜜月旅行 在這種情況下
just doesn't really seem affordable.
還真的付不起了
So, you know, we just thought,
所以 我們就想
just because we can't travel doesn't mean we can't have pictures.
沒錢旅行 不代表不能拍照啊
- I think that's a fabulous idea.  - Yeah, it's a good one.
- 我覺得這個點子棒極了  - 是啊 很棒
I mean the concept is turnkey everything.
我們的理念是一條龍服務
Ok, you buy a maintenance contract when you get the home. You know,
好 當你買下房子就等於買了份維修合約
we'll whack your weeds, we'll change your light bulbs, furniture,
我們替你修剪草坪 換燈泡 還有傢俱
you can bring your own or pick one of our beautiful packages.
你可以用自己的 或者選擇我們的精美套裝
- Seamless traditionalism, yet all the perks.  - Nice.
- 傳承經典 獲益無限  - 不錯啊
We all need a place to call our own. This is America. This is who we were promised.
我們都需要自己的家園 這是美國人的夢想
- It's a nice touch  - What?
- 畫龍點睛  - 什麼?
The bit at the end about the promise. I like that part.
最後"諾言"那句 我喜歡
Oh, thanks.
哦 謝謝
- You er...you still renting that one-bedroom?  - No. I gave it up.
你 呃... 還租住那一居室呢?  - 沒 不了
- So you own now?  - No.
- 那麼你買下了?  - 沒
But you're looking?
但是你一直觀望著?
No, not really.
沒有
So you're just good?
那你現在很好?
- I'm good.  - Well, that's good.
- 我很好  - 哦 那就好
Can you believe it's tomorrow? How are you gonna sleep?
明天你就結婚了? 今晚怎麼能睡著啊?
I don't know.
我也不知道
- Well, do you want some Xanax?  - I don't think that's for sleeping.
- 要不要吃點阿普唑侖?(性藥)  - 那不是有助睡眠的吧
Yeah. No, I think I'll just have a glass of warm milk.
恩 不了 我喝杯溫牛奶吧
- That'll do the trick.  - OK. See you tomorrow.
- 那就夠了  - 好的 明天見
There's another box inside.
裡面還有個箱子
- I'll grab it.  - You sure?
- 我去拿  - 你確定?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
是啊 是啊
- Jim seems like a good guy.  - Yeah, isn't he great?
- Jim看起來很不錯啊  - 是啊 很棒吧?
He's gonna make a great husband.
他會是個好老公
You know, Julie, I was thinking, you know, with dad not being here, erm...
Julie 我在想 老爸不在這裡 呃...
I was wondering if you had anybody to walk you down the aisle.
不知道你有沒有找到人 和你一起步入婚禮殿堂
- No, Jim's uncle is gonna do it.  - He's been really supportive.
- 恩 Jim的叔叔陪我  - 他真的很熱心
He's been great.
他是個好人
Well, good. That's great. I just wanted to make sure that you...
呃 很好 非常好 我就是想確定你...
I wanted you to be covered, that's all.
我想有人照顧你 就這樣
So, I should be there, what?
那麼 我應該幾點到?
The other guests are arriving around five and things get going at five-thirty so...
賓客們五點到 婚禮五點半開始 所以...
- around then.  - OK.
- 那會來吧  - 好的
Oh. Let me... I'm gonna help you with those.
哦 讓我... 幫你拿吧
Got it.
接著了
It's OK. It's OK, it's OK.
沒事的 沒事 沒事
None of that was here.
以前的都不在了
This is all new.
都是新建的
Really?
真的?
- Is that all you got?  - What?
- 你就這點本事?  - 什麼?
Give me a boost.
抬我一下
Watch...
小心點...
Hang on.
等著我
I took Geography in here.
我在這上過地理課
You ever fool around with one of your teachers?
你有沒有和老師亂搞過?
- No. Did you?  - No. Not until college.
- 沒 你有過?  - 沒 大學的時候才幹這事
That's me on the right.
右邊那個是我
- It's kinda hard to tell.  - You can tell by the eyebrows.
- 不好認啊  - 看眉毛就知道了
- You played basketball?  - I was a point guard. Don't act so surprised.
- 你打過籃球?  - 我可是組織後衛(組織後衛是球隊的靈魂) 別吃驚
I didn't know you were such a jock.
沒想到你還是籃球隊的呢
That's me too.
那也是我
And that.
還有那個
- My first fight.  - How'd it go?
- 第一次打架的地方  - 戰績如何?
Got my ass kicked.
被揍得屁滾尿流
- This is where we used to go to make out.  - Oh, yes. Yeah. This is very romantic.
- 這是我們親熱的地兒 - 哦 是啊 恩 好浪漫
- I'm really happy I came here.  - So am I.
- 我很開心和你一起來這  - 我也是
It's Kara. Hi.
是Kara 嘿
Ryan, where are you? We're having a meltdown here.
Ryan 你在哪呢? 出大事了
What's going on? What happened?
怎麼了? 出什麼事了?
It's Jim. Can you get back here? We need your help.
是Jim 你能回來嗎? 需要你幫忙
OK.
好的
We gotta go.
我們得走了
- I'll grab your suit.  - Thanks.
- 我幫你拿衣服  - 謝謝
- What happened?  - Jim's got cold feet.
- 發生什麼了?  - Jim怯場了
- Today?  - Yeah, that's how cold feet work.
- 今天?  - 是的 的確如此
- What do you want me to do?  - Talk to him.
- 你要我做什麼呢?  - 和他談談
- You want me to talk to him?  - Hey, it's either you or me.
- 你要我和他談?  - 喂 這事兒不是你做就是我做
You know my track record. I've already struck out once.
你知道我的過去 我已經失敗過一次了
I haven't been to bat. I haven't been in the dugout.
我一點經驗的都沒有
Don't you talk for a living? Motivational-type stuff?
你不是靠說話謀生的嗎? 勵志類的?
I tell people how to avoid commitment.
我告訴人們怎麼逃避義務
What fuck kind of message is that?
你說的是什麼鬼話?
- It's a philosophy.  - It's stupid.
- 那是生活哲學  - 那太蠢了
- Hey, it could have helped you.  - Ryan.
- 嗨 那也許能幫到你  - Ryan
You haven't been around much. Fuck... Basically, you don't exist to us.
你很少在我們身邊 他媽的... 你根本就沒出現過
I know you wanna be there for her.
我知道你想幫她
Well, here it is. This is your chance.
好 現在正是時候 你的機會來了
Hey. What's up, Ryan?
嗨 怎麼了 Ryan?
- Jim.  - You ever read this before?
- Jim  - 你讀過這本書嗎?
- Yeah, it's pretty powerful stuff...  - I'll say...
- 讀過 那本書很不錯...  - 我也覺得...
Er... Kara mentioned that you were having some thoughts.
呃... Kara說你有一些顧慮
I don't think I'm going to be able to... er... to do this.
我想我沒法... 呃... 和Kara結婚
Why would you say that... today?
你為什麼... 今天才說?
Well, last night I was kinda laying in bed and I couldn't get to sleep.
嗯 昨天晚上我躺在床上睡不著
So I started thinking about the wedding and the ceremony,
我就開始想婚禮 想結婚儀式
and about our buying a house and moving in together.
接著我們買房一起生活
And having a kid, and having another kid and then.
我們會有一個孩子 然後有第二個
Christmas and Thanksgiving and spring break.
聖誕節 感恩節 春假
Going to football games, and then all of a sudden they're graduating.
參加足球比賽 然後轉眼他們就要畢業了
They're getting jobs, getting married. And, you know, I'm a grandparent.
要找工作結婚 然後你知道 我就成爺爺了
And then I'm retired. I'm losing my hair. I'm getting fat.
然後我退休 脫髮 發福
And then the next thing you know I'm dead.
再後來 你想 我就死了
I'm just, like... I can't stop from thinking, what's the point?
我只是 好像... 忍不住去想 那都有什麼意義?
I mean, what is the point?
我是說 意義何在?
- The point?  - I mean, what am I starting here?
- 意義?  - 我意思是 我這是要幹什麼?
Jim, it's... marriage.
Jim 這就是... 婚姻
It's one of the most beautiful things on the earth. It's what people aspire to.
這是世上最美好的事情之一 每個人都嚮往
- You never got married.  - That's true.
- 你都沒有結過婚  - 那倒是
- I mean, you never even tried.  - Well, it's hard to define try.
- 我是說 你甚至都沒有嘗試過  - 嗯 嘗試的定義各有不同
I don't know, just you seem happier than all my married friends.
我不清楚 只是似乎你比我那些已婚的朋友更開心
Look, Jim, I'm not going to lie to you. Marriage can be a pain in the ass.
聽著 Jim 我不想說謊 婚姻很討厭
And you're right. This all is just stuff that leads to your eventual demise.
你是對的 這一切是你走向死亡的過程
- Yes.  - And we're all on running clocks.
- 就是  - 我們都坐在時間的車輪上
And they can't be slowed down or paused.
我們無法放慢或暫停它
- And... we all end up in the same place.  - Yeah.
- 還有... 最終我們的生命都會結束  - 是的
- There is no point.  - There is no point. That's what I'm saying.
- 沒有意義  - 沒有意義 這就是我要說的
You know, er...
你要知道 呃...
I'm not normally the guy you would talk to about stuff like this.
我通常不會跟你說這些事情
If you think about it...
但你試想下...
Your favourite memories, the most important moments in your life.
你人生中最珍貴的回憶 最重要的時刻
Were you alone?
是獨自一人嗎?
No, I guess not.
不 我想不是的
Come to think of it.
再想想這個
Last night, the night before your wedding when all this shit is swirling around in your head,
昨晚 婚禮前夜 當這些該死的想法縈繞在你的腦海時
weren't you guys in separate bedroom?
你是在單人間裡嗎?
Yeah, Julie went back to the apartment and I was just by myself in the honeymoon suite.
是 Julie回公寓了 我呆在蜜月套房裡
- Kinda lonely, huh?  - Yes, it was pretty lonely.
- 是不是有點孤單?  - 是的 挺孤單
Life's better with company.
所以 有伴侶的人生才更美好
- Yeah...  - Everybody needs a co-pilot.
- 是的...  - 每個人都需要有個人扶持
- That was a nice touch.  - Thanks.
- 說的好  - 謝謝
- So er... what's the mood like out there?  - It's not good.
- 所以 呃 她在外邊心情怎樣?  - 不好
- She's pretty pissed?  - Just upset.
- 她是不是很生氣?  - 就是有點難過
What should I do?
我該怎麼辦?
Go get her.
去找她
I'm such a fuck-up. I love you so much.
我是個混蛋 我那麼愛你
Will you be my co-pilot?
你願意陪我共度餘生嗎?
Yes. Yes.
願意 願意
Welcome home.
歡迎回家
OK, this is your stop.
嗯 你到了
- When am I gonna see you?  - You're just gonna have to come visit.
- 我什麼時候能再見到你?  - 你過來就行
Oh... so settled.
哦... 安頓下來了
- You're not gonna change on me, are you?  - No. Same guy. Just one address.
- 你會因為我而改變了吧 是嗎?  - 不 人沒變 只多個地址
This is your final boarding call for Flight 3972 to Chicago.
飛往芝加哥的3972號航班就要起飛了
Right. Call me when you get lonely.
好吧 寂寞的時候給我打電話
I'm lonely.
我寂寞了
Some guy sits in a conference room somewhere
員工們坐在會議室裡
and our server routes his session to one of our termination engineers.
我們的服務器會把將他們分配給我們的終結工程師
"Termination engineers"? Really?
"終結工程師"? 是嗎?
I preferred "terminators" but it bumped with Legal.
我更喜歡"終結者" 但怕引起法律糾紛
Can't imagine why.
難以置信
The workflow takes them through anything from a standard dismissal to a violent aggressor.
工作流程會訓練工程師們應付各種被解雇者
What are they doing now, practising?
他們現在在做什麼 練習嗎?
Beta testing, role-playing. We go live at the end of the month.
公開測試 角色扮演 這個月底要投入實際使用
Kyle, you're running through the events too quickly.
Kyle 你說的太快了
Give them time to acknowledge each statement. It's a legal thing.
給他們點時間接受你的陳述 這是合法的
- Ryan?  - Mm? Oh. Yeah. There's more?
- Ryan?  - 嗯? 好 還有嗎?
This is ridiculous.
這太荒唐了
Legal's starting to come hard at me on this term "terminate"...
"終止"這個詞的合法化讓我很難接受...
Life to the power of you!
活出你的精彩!
Ladies and gentlemen. Put your hands together for today's challenge speaker,
先生們 女士們 掌聲歡迎今天的演講挑戰者
Mr Ryan Bingham
Ryan Bingham先生
Go get 'em.
好好表現
Last year I flew 350,000 miles.
去年 我飛行了35萬英里
The moon is 250.
地球到月球也就25萬英里
I want you to imagine for a second that you're carrying a backpack.
試想下 當你帶著行李
I want you to feel the straps on your shoulders.
你感受下肩上承受的重量
You feel 'em?
感受到了嗎?
Now I want you to pack it with all the stuff that you have in your life.
而我想讓你們將生命的一切裝入行囊
Start with the little things. The things on shelves and in drawers.
從小東西開始... 架子上或是抽屜裡的
Excuse me.
抱歉
What the fuck are you doing?
你他媽的在幹嗎?
Relax. We'll have your next guest out in one sec.
稍安勿躁 我們馬上有請下一位演講者
- Hey, you gotta sign.  - OK.
- 嗨 你得簽字  - 行
OK, thank you.
嗯 謝謝
Hey, you forgot to give me your Hertz No.1 Gold Card!
喂 你忘了給我Hertz(美國汽車租賃巨頭)的貴賓金卡!
So I was in the neighbourhood.
我正好在這附近
- Hey, honey, who's at the door?  - Just somebody who's lost.
- 親愛的 誰敲門?  - 過路的 他迷路了
Alex?
Alex?
What were you thinking, showing up at my door like that?
你在想什麼 就這麼出現在我家門口?
What do you mean? I wanted to see you. I didn't know you had a family.
你什麼意思? 我想見你 我不知道你有家庭
Why didn't you tell me that?
你為什麼不告訴我?
Sorry I ruined your evening but you could have screwed things up for me.
很抱歉毀了你的夜晚 但是你也差點毀掉了我的生活
That's my family. That's my real life.
那是我的家人 我真正的生活
I thought I was a part of your real life.
我還以為我們初衷相同呢
I thought we signed up for the same thing.
我以為我們想法一致
Try and help me understand exactly what it is that you signed up for.
跟我說說你的初衷
I thought our relationship was perfectly clear. I mean...
我想我們的關係很明確 我是說...
you are an escape.
你是我的逃避
You're a break from our normal lives, you're a...
你是我正常生活的一種調劑 就像...
a parenthesis.
一段插曲
I'm a parenthesis?
我是一段插曲?
I mean... what do you want?
我是說... 你想要什麼?
Tell me what you want.
告訴我你想要什麼
You don't even know what you want.
你根本就不知道你要什麼
Ryan, I'm a grown-up, OK?
Ryan 我是成年人了 好嗎?
So if you would like to see me again, then then give me a call.
如果你還想見我 給我電話
OK?
好嗎?
Ladies and gentlemen, we have a special announcement to make.
先生們 女士們 下面播放一則特別通告
Our pilot has just informed me that we are passing over the city of Dubuque,
機長告訴我 我們將要飛過迪比克市
which might not mean much to most of you, but means a lot to one of our flyers today.
也許對大家毫無意義 但對一位乘客卻意義非凡
- Oh, no.  - Because he just hit 10 million miles!
- 哦 不要  - 他的飛行里程突破了1000萬英里!
- Congratulations.  - Such an amazing accomplishment.
- 祝賀你  - 如此驚人的數字
You must be very excited.
你一定很激動吧
- Hi, Captain.  - Captain.
- 機長好  - 機長
That seat taken?
那個位子有人嗎?
No. No.
沒 沒有
You're the youngest yet to hit 10 mil.
你是突破1000萬英里中最年輕的人
Don't know where you found the time.
不知道你是怎麼擠出時間來的
Yeah. I don't know.
我也不知道
Here you go.
這給你
Seventh card we've made.
我們製作的第七張卡
Small club.
很少人擁有它
We really appreciate your loyalty.
我們由衷感謝您的支持
You know how many times I thought about this moment?
你知道 我曾多少次夢想這一刻?
Played out the conversation that you and I would have right here.
幻想著你和我在這裡談話
Really?
真的嗎?
What did you want to say?
那你想說什麼?
You know, I don't remember.
我不記得了
That's all right. It happens to all of us.
沒關係 這很正常
So where are you from?
你哪裡人?
I'm from here.
我屬於這裡
Hello, Mr Bingham.
你好 Bingham先生
How did you know it was me?
你怎麼知道是我?
This is your dedicated line. We reserve them for our most loyal and appreciated flyers.
這是您的專線 我們為頂級會員提供的
I'd like to transfer some of my miles. Can I open up an account to Jim and Julie Miller?
我想轉換一些我的里程數 我能否為Jim和Julie Miller開個賬戶?
Certainly. How many miles would you like to transfer?
可以 你想轉換多少?
How many miles does it take to circle the globe?
周遊世界要多少里程數?
We have our round-the-world tickets. They're 500,000 miles each.
我們有周遊世界的套票 每張需要50萬英里
- That'd be fine.  - Got a second?
- 好的  - 有時間嗎?
I'll call you back.
我過會兒打給你
What happened to you yesterday? I was trying to get hold of you.
你昨天幹嘛去了? 我到處找你
I was some personal stuff. What's going on?
處理些私事 怎麼了?
Do you remember Karen Barnes,
你還記得Karen Barnes嗎
part of a 30-person reduction a few weeks back in Wichita?
幾周前 在威奇托市辭掉的30個人之一?
- Natalie fired her.  - Fired dozens of people a day. I...
- Natalie解雇了她  - 那天裁了很多人 我...
She killed herself... jumped off a bridge.
她自殺了... 從橋上跳了下去
Fuck.
我靠
I need to know if you remember any woman that gave you any signals,
我要知道 那位女士給過你什麼暗示
- depression...  - They're all depressed. We're firing them.
- 沮喪...  - 他們都很沮喪 我們讓解雇了他們
- Hey, I need to ask you this stuff, OK?  - No, I don't remember anything.
- 喂 我要弄清楚 明白?  - 不 我什麼都不記得了
You never think that they're...
你不會想他們...
You don't remember any woman that gave you any signals?
你不記得那個女的給過你暗示?
- Anything at all, Ryan?  - No, nothing stands out.
- 一點都沒有 Ryan?  - 沒有 沒有什麼異常
- Is Natalie all right?  - Natalie quit.
- Natalie正常嗎?  - Natalie辭職了
- She quit?  - Text message.
- 她辭職了?  - 通過短信
Fucking nice, right? No-one's got any manners any more.
不錯啊 是吧? 一點禮儀都不講
- Did she say where she was going?  - No. She was a little upset.
- 她說要去哪兒嗎?  - 沒有 就是看起來有些難過
I should give her a call.
我應該給她打個電話
I need you back in the air.
我需要你回來 在空中工作
Hey. Did you hear what I said? I thought you'd be thrilled about that.
你聽到我說的了嗎? 我還以為你會很興奮呢
It's fine. What about the videoconferencing?
沒事 那個視頻裁人呢?
CTC is going to pause the new media front. They're gonna give it some more thought.
付款中心要停止新媒體的投資 他們決定再考慮考慮
We are gonna get our workhorses back in the air doing what they do best, OK?
我們要召回我們的老黃牛來重操舊業 可以嗎?
How long are you sending me out?
這次要派我出去多久?
We're gonna let you sail and sail. You send us a postcard if you ever get there.
你想去多久都行 到個地方 就給我們寄張明信片
So what happened?
發生什麼了?
How exactly do you mean?
這麼問什麼意思?
You graduated top of your class.
你是班上的尖子生
You seemed to have your pick of employment, including here.
你似乎都做好了職業規劃 包括這裡
Instead you went to Omaha to fire people for a living?
但是你卻去了奧馬哈 靠裁員為生?
- It's challenging work.  - I'll say!
- 這是一份有挑戰性的工作  - 我也會這麼說!
I can't imagine doing that, day in, day out.
我無法想像做那種工作 日復一日
Not in this climate.
現在不景氣
I followed a boy.
我為了一個男孩去的
I guess everybody does that at one point or another.
我想每個人 都會因為這樣或那樣的理由
This guy says I'd be lucky to have you.
這個人說 能雇到你是種幸運
To whom it may concern.
致相關人員
I can't even count the number of people I've fired in my lifetime.
我一生中解雇的人不計其數
So many that I've actually forgotten what it's like to hire somebody.
以至於我都想不起僱人的感覺
We've never met, but I know you'd be lucky to have Natalie Keener.
我們未曾相識 但是你聘用Natalie Keener會是一種幸運
My advice? Take her and don't look back.
問我的建議? 聘用她 不要猶豫
She'll be the best decision you've made in a long time.
這會是你們的最好選擇
I sure hope he's right.
希望他是對的
Well, I don't have a lot of hope,
嗯 我不抱期望
and I really don't know when it's gonna get better.
也不知道未來是否會好轉
There's a lot of people unemployed.
有很多人待業
And I really don't know when there's gonna be light at the end of the tunnel.
真不知道什麼時候才能看到曙光
I can't find much to talk about.
我沒什麼好說的
Talk about being proud. I'm proud of my kids.
要說自豪 我為我的孩子感到自豪
I think the anger comes from the fact that I just wasn't needed any more.
我認為憤怒 因為不再被人需要
I would say, you know, uh...
我想說 呃...
without my friends and my family,
要不是朋友和家人的支持
I wouldn't have made it.
我無法堅持下來
It would have been a lot tougher if I'd had to make it on my own.
如果只有我一個人 我想那會舉步維艱
When I wake up in the morning and I look over and I see my wife,
當我早上醒來 看到妻子
that gives me the sense of purpose.
讓我鼓起生活的勇氣
It's not all about the money. Money can keep you warm.
那並不是錢的問題 錢能讓你溫暖
It pays your heating bills. It can buy you a blanket.
為你付暖氣費 為你買毛毯
But it doesn't keep you as warm as when my husband holds me.
但是它遠不及我丈夫的懷抱
Let me get up. Let me get out. Let me find something.
讓我起床 讓我出門 讓我找活幹
So my kids are my purpose. My family.
我的孩子和家人給了我決心
Tonight most people will be welcomed home by jumping dogs and squealing kids.
今夜人們回家 迎接他們的是歡呼雀躍的小狗和孩子們
Their spouses will ask about their day and tonight they'll sleep.
他們的愛人會噓寒問暖 然後安然入眠
The stars will wheel forth from their daytime hiding places.
斗轉星移 夜幕低垂
And one of those lights, slightly brighter than the rest,
有一束光 格外耀眼
will be my wing tip passing over.
那是我的機翼劃過的痕跡
Hi, Jason. My name is Kevin. And I recently lost my job.
嗨 Jason 我叫Kevin 我最近失業了
I wrote this song as sort of a statement about uncertainty
我寫了首歌 來表達我的不確定
and having a certain amount of anxiety about the future.
和對未來的焦慮
So maybe you can use it in your movie.
希望能夠配你的電影